[{"id":0,"question":"7-6","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":1,"question":"4-2","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"question":"8-6","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"question":"9-2","choices":[6,7,8],"rightAnswer":7,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"question":"6-3","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":5,"question":"2-1","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":6,"question":"8-0","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":7,"question":"8-0","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":8,"question":"8-7","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":9,"question":"9-6","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":10,"question":"3-0","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":11,"question":"6-4","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":12,"question":"8-5","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":13,"question":"6-4","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":14,"question":"7-1","choices":[5,6,7],"rightAnswer":6,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":15,"question":"6-5","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":16,"question":"6-3","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":17,"question":"8-6","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":18,"question":"1-0","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":19,"question":"7-6","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":20,"question":"27-5","choices":[21,22,23],"rightAnswer":22,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":21,"question":"66-8","choices":[57,58,59],"rightAnswer":58,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":22,"question":"47-8","choices":[38,39,40],"rightAnswer":39,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":23,"question":"75-4","choices":[70,71,72],"rightAnswer":71,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":24,"question":"75-6","choices":[68,69,70],"rightAnswer":69,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":25,"question":"32-7","choices":[24,25,26],"rightAnswer":25,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":26,"question":"48-6","choices":[41,42,43],"rightAnswer":42,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":27,"question":"55-5","choices":[49,50,51],"rightAnswer":50,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":28,"question":"26-2","choices":[23,24,25],"rightAnswer":24,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":29,"question":"83-5","choices":[77,78,79],"rightAnswer":78,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":30,"question":"45-4","choices":[40,41,42],"rightAnswer":41,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":31,"question":"37-4","choices":[32,33,34],"rightAnswer":33,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":32,"question":"96-5","choices":[90,91,92],"rightAnswer":91,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":33,"question":"16-4","choices":[11,12,13],"rightAnswer":12,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":34,"question":"30-1","choices":[28,29,30],"rightAnswer":29,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":35,"question":"81-2","choices":[78,79,80],"rightAnswer":79,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":36,"question":"96-4","choices":[91,92,93],"rightAnswer":92,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":37,"question":"84-2","choices":[81,82,83],"rightAnswer":82,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":38,"question":"30-9","choices":[20,21,22],"rightAnswer":21,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":39,"question":"42-5","choices":[36,37,38],"rightAnswer":37,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":40,"question":"90-47","choices":[42,43,44],"rightAnswer":43,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":41,"question":"85-33","choices":[51,52,53],"rightAnswer":52,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":42,"question":"48-47","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":43,"question":"92-61","choices":[30,31,32],"rightAnswer":31,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":44,"question":"68-67","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":45,"question":"64-33","choices":[30,31,32],"rightAnswer":31,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":46,"question":"47-28","choices":[18,19,20],"rightAnswer":19,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":47,"question":"47-10","choices":[36,37,38],"rightAnswer":37,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":48,"question":"77-46","choices":[30,31,32],"rightAnswer":31,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":49,"question":"48-34","choices":[13,14,15],"rightAnswer":14,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":50,"question":"99-38","choices":[60,61,62],"rightAnswer":61,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":51,"question":"95-91","choices":[3,4,5],"rightAnswer":4,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":52,"question":"75-14","choices":[60,61,62],"rightAnswer":61,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":53,"question":"60-45","choices":[14,15,16],"rightAnswer":15,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":54,"question":"96-73","choices":[22,23,24],"rightAnswer":23,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":55,"question":"78-27","choices":[50,51,52],"rightAnswer":51,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":56,"question":"64-31","choices":[32,33,34],"rightAnswer":33,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":57,"question":"64-23","choices":[40,41,42],"rightAnswer":41,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":58,"question":"86-82","choices":[3,4,5],"rightAnswer":4,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":59,"question":"97-96","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":60,"question":"512-30","choices":[481,482,483],"rightAnswer":482,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":61,"question":"806-63","choices":[742,743,744],"rightAnswer":743,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":62,"question":"565-82","choices":[482,483,484],"rightAnswer":483,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":63,"question":"823-57","choices":[765,766,767],"rightAnswer":766,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":64,"question":"546-59","choices":[486,487,488],"rightAnswer":487,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":65,"question":"882-72","choices":[809,810,811],"rightAnswer":810,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":66,"question":"898-52","choices":[845,846,847],"rightAnswer":846,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":67,"question":"928-14","choices":[913,914,915],"rightAnswer":914,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":68,"question":"226-29","choices":[196,197,198],"rightAnswer":197,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":69,"question":"911-45","choices":[865,866,867],"rightAnswer":866,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":70,"question":"988-11","choices":[976,977,978],"rightAnswer":977,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":71,"question":"841-37","choices":[803,804,805],"rightAnswer":804,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":72,"question":"510-27","choices":[482,483,484],"rightAnswer":483,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":73,"question":"733-17","choices":[715,716,717],"rightAnswer":716,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":74,"question":"590-95","choices":[494,495,496],"rightAnswer":495,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":75,"question":"432-27","choices":[404,405,406],"rightAnswer":405,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":76,"question":"852-98","choices":[753,754,755],"rightAnswer":754,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":77,"question":"599-86","choices":[512,513,514],"rightAnswer":513,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":78,"question":"101-75","choices":[25,26,27],"rightAnswer":26,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":79,"question":"909-24","choices":[884,885,886],"rightAnswer":885,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":80,"question":"701-693","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":81,"question":"684-382","choices":[301,302,303],"rightAnswer":302,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":82,"question":"804-328","choices":[475,476,477],"rightAnswer":476,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":83,"question":"560-460","choices":[99,100,101],"rightAnswer":100,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":84,"question":"686-647","choices":[38,39,40],"rightAnswer":39,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":85,"question":"856-287","choices":[568,569,570],"rightAnswer":569,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":86,"question":"987-309","choices":[677,678,679],"rightAnswer":678,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":87,"question":"891-806","choices":[84,85,86],"rightAnswer":85,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":88,"question":"828-308","choices":[519,520,521],"rightAnswer":520,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":89,"question":"954-641","choices":[312,313,314],"rightAnswer":313,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":90,"question":"799-349","choices":[449,450,451],"rightAnswer":450,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":91,"question":"736-438","choices":[297,298,299],"rightAnswer":298,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":92,"question":"629-204","choices":[424,425,426],"rightAnswer":425,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":93,"question":"867-407","choices":[459,460,461],"rightAnswer":460,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":94,"question":"970-698","choices":[271,272,273],"rightAnswer":272,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":95,"question":"382-348","choices":[33,34,35],"rightAnswer":34,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":96,"question":"864-400","choices":[463,464,465],"rightAnswer":464,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":97,"question":"265-158","choices":[106,107,108],"rightAnswer":107,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":98,"question":"534-343","choices":[190,191,192],"rightAnswer":191,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":99,"question":"717-438","choices":[278,279,280],"rightAnswer":279,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false}]